You're glowing, you cover and fracture the light
You can't help but shine and I know that
You carry the world on your back, but look at you tonight
The lights, your face, your eyes, exploding like fire
Works in the sky, set fire
Don't you know your body, why you pushing on me?
Don't you know your body, I could do this all week
We'll be dancing till the morning, go to baby, won't sleep
Tum, tum, tum, tum, tits, it's dirty body, body, game fire
Don't you know your body, why you pushing on me?
Don't you know your body, I could do this all week?
We'll be dancing till the morning, go to baby, won't sleep
Tum, tum, tum, tum, tits, it's dirty body, game
Look what we found, come and reach down
Into our hearts and pull us to our feet now
You know the truth is, we could disappear
Anywhere, as long as I got you there
When the sun dies, till the day shines
When I'm with you, it's not enough time
You're on my spring flower, watching you bloom wild
We y'all surrounding, but I can only see the lights
Your face, your eyes, exploding like fire
Works in the sky, set fire
Don't you know your body, why you pushing on me?
Don't you know your body, I could do this all week?
We'll be dancing till the morning, go to baby, won't sleep
Tum, tum, tum, tum, tits, it's dirty body, body, game fire
Don't you know your body, why you pushing on me?
Don't you know your body, I could do this all week?
We'll be dancing till the morning, go to baby, won't sleep
Tum, tum, tum, tum, tits, it's dirty body, game fire
Don't you know your body, why you pushing on me?
You come here and distract you, the light, look at you tonight
Set fire, let's go to the sky, let's go to the sky
Don't you know your body, why you pushing on me?
Don't you know your body, I could do this all week?
We'll be dancing till the morning, go to baby, won't sleep
Tum, tum, tum, tum, tits, it's dirty body, body, game fire
Don't you know your body, why you pushing on me?
Don't you know your body, I could do this all week?
Shut the lights, your face, your eyes, it's flowing like fire
Worms in the sky, shut the lights